Minami Koma

WEB DEVELOPER

📞 +17782513672 | 🖂 minamikoma24@gmail.com | 🏕 minamikoma.me/mysite/ | 🔾 minami-k | in minami-koma

Summary _

Front-end developer with a background and passion for user experience and interaction design and strength in creative and strategic thinking. Learning and growing as a developer are very important to me. Since 2020, I have continuously gained new development skills and never stopped challenging my potential, while creating accessible and aesthetic websites. I am excellent at working in teams and enjoy collaboration with peers. I am also confident in the development of the front-end for e-commerce sites and will do my best to deliver modern interfaces.

Skills

Skills

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, WordPress, PHP, Shopify, TypeScript, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Firebase, GitHub

Experience _____

PIPELINE, Inc. Kobe, Japan

WEB DEVELOPER (TECHNOLOGIES USED: HTML, CSS, WORDPRESS, SHOPIFY, JAVASCRIPT)

July 2020 - April 2022

- Created user interfaces with HTML, CSS and jQuery, which increased user satisfaction by 40 percent.
 Curated 30+ company websites to improve user engagement.
- Transferred a conventional website to EC site with WooCommerce which increased sales by 35 percent.
- Collaborated with the marketing and design team, which allowed me not only to respond to clients' needs but also to gain excellent written and oral communication skills.

Accessnet Remote

Web developer/ Web designer (technologies used: HTML, CSS, Wordpress, Php, Adobe XD)

October 2020 - April 2022

- Developed over 10 websites for companies in different industries.
- Created responsive and functional websites to allow visitors from any device to have the same stress-free user experience.
- · Utilized and customized modern WordPress themes, which improved efficiency in developing websites by 60 percent.

Projects _____

Hong Knog Charo

SKILL USED: HTML, CSS, WORDPRESS(CUSTOM THEME), WORDPRESS PLUGINS

 An official website for a Chinese restaurant located in Japan. I coded from a mock-up which a design team created. (https://www.hk-charo.com)

Personal Dashboard

SKILL USED: HTML, CSS, TAILWIND CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, REACT HOOKS, WEATHER API, NEW YORK TIMES API

• Created this for personal use. It has everything I need; a task list, weather forecast, news, time, and date. Now I don't need to switch screens to check each information.

(https://github.com/minami-k/dashboard)

Uber Clone

SKILL USED: HTML, CSS, SASS

 Cloned an official Uber website to test my accuracy of styling. (https://github.com/minami-k/clonesite)

Education

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

DIPLOMA IN WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

Course taken: React.js/ Node.js/ SASS JavaScript

Osaka, Japan

May 2021

April 2015 - March 2019

Vancouver, Canada

Kansai University

BACHELOR IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE STUDIES

• Major: intercultural communication